

DANIL VOLOSYUK

Senior Frontend Engineer

My experience at the web development is 4 years. I have large experience in web application development, including creating the architecture of the client and server sides, configuring builds, pipelines and deploying apps to cloud services.

Besides that, I think soft skills are just as important as hard skills. Therefore, I am open to feedback and always try to be a good team member. Also can call myself a fast-growing, responsible and multi-tasking person.

CONTACT

- daniil.volosyuk@gmail.com
- danyavol.dev
- t.me/d4nvol
- in linkedin.com/in/danyavol
- github.com/danyavol

SKILLS

TypeScript JavaScript Angular

Vue React

Angular Material

RxJS

SASS/SCSS CSS HTML Less

Taiga UI Semantic UI ApexCharts

Bootstrap

Bulma

Jasmine

BitBucket

Google Charts Husky pre-commit

TFS Webpack Git Docker

NgRx Capacitor Karma Ionic Jest

Redux

TeamCity Azure DevOps Heroku

Netlify GitHub Actions Firebase

GitLab Railway Figma Jira

Hotjar Newrelic i18n

Google Analytics

Google Play Console

MongoDB Node.js Express

PostgreSQL JWT mongoose

cheerio

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2021 current



Frontend Engineer

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - MINSK, WARSAW

Call Center project

The call center with huge configuration, possibility for inbound and outbound calls, and many other features useful for agents.

- Migrated the legacy JS code to Vue.js 3
- Worked closely with the client's team, 90% of communication was in English
- Worked with Azure pipelines

Technologies: Vue.js 2 and 3.4, Vuex, Pinia, TypeScript, Vite, Vitest, ESLint, SCSS, Sip.js, WebSockets(SignalR), Azure DevOps.

Datacenters project

The project is about cloud services, security, datacenters, giving servers in rent, physical access to datacenters. Also it has 3 sub-projects and I worked there, too.

- Migrated pages from Angular.js to Angular 9
- Updated Angular version from 9 to 14
- Performed deployment on staging environment
- Refactored existing forms and pages
- Worked with forms, charts, widgets
- Analyzed and improved app performance, bundled size reduction
- Created designs of new components and new features, suggested UI and UX improvements
- Set up Angular library with shared components across client sub-projects
- Worked with CI in TeamCity, configured build pipelines in Azure DevOps, restrictions for PRs, branches security
- Meetings with the client. Knowledge transfer meetings for Coherent team and for client team
- Work with payments, financial reports and bills

Have used such technologies as: Typescript, Angular.js, Angular 9-14, Git, TFS, Azure DevOps, TeamCity, RxJs, ApexCharts, Google Charts, Google Maps, Angular Material, ESLint, Jasmine, Karma, Quill

Internal projects

Worked on two internal company projects.

Tools, Environment, Languages and Technologies: TypeScript, Angular, NgRx, RxJs, Jira

Oct 2020 -Feb 2021

Frontend Developer

PRIVATE CLIENT FROM CANADA

Developed a front-end part of the control panel of the company to be used by employees (add/edit products, contacts, events; statistics, dashboards, etc.) and helped a little bit with back-end part.

jQuery, HTML, CSS, JS, Front (Bootstrap 4 based template), Java, Spring.

2018-current

Personal Projects

Besides the work I got paid for, I have a lot of fun and useful personal projects, some of them have become really successful. I got a lot of knowledge and experience from it, highly recommend to visit my personal page (https://danyavol.dev) and check the most remarkable projects.

EDUCATION

Dec 2023 O Security Testing Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Jun 2023

Node.js

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Mar 2023

React Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Apr 2021

Angular Training

COHERENT SOLUTIONS - INTERNAL TRAINING

Feb 2019 -Dec 2019 Frontend Developer Courses

IT ACADEMY STEP - MINSK

During the course I have learned all basic technologies needed to apply for Junior Frontend position and a little bit more. Also learned basics of Angular and React frameworks.

2018 - 2022

Bachelor's Degree

INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY MITSO

Specialization - Information systems and technologies



- English (B2 Level)
- Russian (Native)
- Belarusian (Native)
- Polish (A1 Level)